<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!-- 
█████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████

  Do not bother submitting translations to the A3W GitHub repo, the strings below are only a tiny fraction of all messages used in the mission.

█████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████
-->
<Project name="Wasteland">
	<Package name="General">
		<Key ID="STR_WL_Gen_TeamWEST">
			<English>BLUFOR</English>
		</Key>
		<Key ID="STR_WL_Gen_TeamWEST_2">
			<English>BLUFOR</English>
		</Key>
		<Key ID="STR_WL_Gen_TeamEAST">
			<English>OPFOR</English>
		</Key>
		<Key ID="STR_WL_Gen_TeamEAST_2">
			<English>OPFOR</English>
		</Key>
		<Key ID="STR_WL_Gen_TeamGUER">
			<English>Independent</English>
			<Spanish>Independiente</Spanish>
		</Key>
		<Key ID="STR_WL_Gen_TeamGUER_2">
			<English>Independent</English>
			<Spanish>Independiente</Spanish>
		</Key>
	</Package>
	<Package name="TeamLock">
		<Key ID="STR_WL_Punish_Teamkiller">
			<English>You have been punished for teamkilling twice during this server session. Your inventory has been wiped, and you are now locked to the Independent side.</English>
			<Spanish>Has sido Penalizado por Fuego Amigo dos veces durante esta sesión. Tu inventario ha sido borrado, y estarás restringido como Independiente.</Spanish>
		</Key>
		<Key ID="STR_WL_Loading_Teamkiller">
			<English>You are restricted to the Independent side, due to having done 2 or more teamkills during this server session.</English>
			<Spanish>Has sido restringido a jugar como Independiente dado que has cometido 2 o más Fuego Amigo durante esta sesión.</Spanish>
		</Key>
		<Key ID="STR_WL_Loading_Teamswitched">
			<English>You have played as %1 for too long and cannot switch to the other team. You can still play as Independent. (or if online, ask an admin to unlock you)</English>
			<Spanish>Has jugado mucho tiempo como %1 y no puedes cambiar de equipo. Aún así puedes jugar como Independiente si lo deseas. (o si hay un Admin conectado pídele que te desbloquee)</Spanish>
		</Key>
	</Package>
	<Package name="WelcomeMessage">
		<Key ID="STR_WL_WelcomeToWasteland">
			<English>&lt;t color='#FF8000' size='2.5' &gt;HC A3Wasteland Altis v1.4D.0.4 &lt;/t&gt;</English>
		</Key>
		<Key ID="STR_WL_YouAreInTeam">
			<English>&lt;t color='#FFFFFF' size='1' &gt;* You are on &lt;img size="1" image="%1"/&gt; &lt;t color="%2"&gt;%3&lt;/t&gt; team.&lt;br/&gt;* Attacking or stealing from %4 players is &lt;t color="#FF1111"&gt;FORBIDDEN!&lt;/t&gt;&lt;br/&gt;* &lt;t color="#FF1111"&gt;NO SPAM IN CHAT!&lt;/t&gt;&lt;br/&gt;</English>
			<Spanish>&lt;t color='#FFFFFF' size='1' &gt;* Eres &lt;img size="1" image="%1"/&gt; &lt;t color="%2"&gt;%3&lt;/t&gt; team.&lt;br/&gt;* Atacar o robar a otros jugadores %4 está &lt;t color="#FF1111"&gt;PROHIBIDO!&lt;/t&gt;&lt;br/&gt;* &lt;t color="#FF1111"&gt;NO HAGA SPAM EN EL CHAT!&lt;/t&gt;&lt;br/&gt;</Spanish>
		</Key>
		<Key ID="STR_WL_YouAreInFFA">
			<English>&lt;t color='#FFFFFF' size='1' &gt;* You are on &lt;img size="1" image="%1"/&gt; &lt;t color="%2"&gt;%3&lt;/t&gt; team.&lt;br/&gt;* You are &lt;t color="#00aa00"&gt;FREE TO ATTACK ANYONE!&lt;/t&gt;&lt;br/&gt;* &lt;t color="#FF1111"&gt;NO SPAM IN CHAT!&lt;/t&gt;&lt;br/&gt;</English>
			<Spanish>&lt;t color='#FFFFFF' size='1' &gt;* Eres &lt;img size="1" image="%1"/&gt; &lt;t color="%2"&gt;%3&lt;/t&gt; team.&lt;br/&gt;* Eres &lt;t color="#00aa00"&gt;LIBRE DE ATACAR Y ROBAR A TODOS!&lt;/t&gt;&lt;br/&gt;* &lt;t color="#FF1111"&gt;NO HAGA SPAM EN EL CHAT!&lt;/t&gt;&lt;br/&gt;</Spanish>
		</Key>
		<Key ID="STR_WL_MapMoreInfo">
			<English>&lt;t color='#FFFFFF' size='1' &gt;CHANGING TEAMS IS PROHIBITED, except to Independent.&lt;br/&gt;If you want to change factions, consult an admin.&lt;br/&gt;EVERYONE is required to be in the TaskForceRadio channel on TeamSpeak.&lt;br/&gt;</English>
			<Spanish>&lt;t color='#FFFFFF' size='1' &gt;CAMBIAR DE EQUIPO ESTÁ PROHIBIDO, excepto hacia Independiente.&lt;br/&gt;Si deseas cambiar de facción, consulta con un admin.&lt;br/&gt;TODOS deben estar en el canal TaskForceRadio en TeamSpeak.&lt;br/&gt;</Spanish>
		</Key>
	</Package>
	<Package name="TeamKillWarningMessage">
		<Key ID="STR_TK_MESSAGE">
			<English>&lt;t size='2' color='#ff0000'&gt;Team killing is against the rules!&lt;/t&gt;&lt;br/&gt;If this was a mistake then you must explain yourself and say sorry, otherwise they will mark you as teamkiller and you will get kicked.</English>
			<Spanish>&lt;t size='2' color='#ff0000'&gt;El Fuego Amigo es en contra de las reglas!&lt;/t&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Si fue por un error Ud. debe explicarse y disculparse, de otro modo te marcarán por Fuego Amigo y se te expulsará de la sesión.</Spanish>
		</Key>
	</Package>
	<Package name="Diary">
		<Key ID="STR_WL_Diary_RulesContent">
			<English>&lt;br/&gt;    1. Keep bad language to a minimum. If you have a problem with another player, take it to direct.&lt;br/&gt;    2. NO VOIP IN GLOBAL. Use the channels or Teamspeak!.&lt;br/&gt;    3. Team killing when you are on BLUFOR or OPFOR is forbidden and punishable. Play as Independent if you want to be free for all.&lt;br/&gt;    4. Revealing information about your (ex)team to other teams is lame and not appreciated&lt;br/&gt;    5. Do not exploit R3F or any other add-ons or you will be banned.&lt;br/&gt;    6. Using or spamming with loud\long custom sound commands will cause punishment up to permanent ban</English>
			<Spanish>&lt;br/&gt;    1. Modere su lenguaje. Si tienes problemas con otro jugador, resuélvalo fuera del server.&lt;br/&gt;    2. NO ESCRIBA EN CHAT GLOBAL. Use Teamspeak o PM!.&lt;br/&gt;    3. El Fuego Amigo cuando eres BLUFOR o OPFOR está prohibido y es castigable. Si quieres matar a todo lo que se te cruce, juega Independiente.&lt;br/&gt;    4. Revelar información de tu equipo anterior a otros no será apreciado ni tolerado&lt;br/&gt;    5. No se aproveche de los errores del juego, será considerado como TRAMPA y serás baneado indefinidamente.&lt;br/&gt;    6. Puede ser baneado por hacer SPAM o crear ruidos molestos y distractivos fuera del diseño del juego.</Spanish>
		</Key>
	</Package>
	<Package name="ShopDescriptions">
		<Key ID="STR_WL_ShopDescriptions_Water">
			<English>Greece is a hot place! Drink plenty!</English>
			<Spanish>Grecia es un lugar caluroso! Beba mucha agua!</Spanish>
		</Key>
		<Key ID="STR_WL_ShopDescriptions_Camo">
			<English>An improvised roof, 4 sticks and a blanket!</English>
		</Key>
		<Key ID="STR_WL_ShopDescriptions_CanFood">
			<English>The Greek wastelands may leave you feeling hungry! Stock up on MRE to keep yourself nourished.</English>
			<Spanish>¡Los yermos griegos pueden dejarte con hambre! Abastécete de MRE para mantenerte nutrido.</Spanish>
		</Key>
		<Key ID="STR_WL_ShopDescriptions_RepairKit">
			<English>With this kit, you won't need an engineer! It includes all the necessary tools and spare parts to fix any vehicle issues on your own.</English>
			<Spanish>¡Con este kit, no necesitarás a un ingeniero! Incluye todas las herramientas y piezas de repuesto necesarias para solucionar cualquier problema del vehículo por tu cuenta.</Spanish>
		</Key>
		<Key ID="STR_WL_ShopDescriptions_MedKit">
			<English>With this kit, you won't need a medic! It includes all the necessary medical supplies to treat injuries and ailments on your own.</English>
			<Spanish>¡Con este kit, no necesitarás un médico! Incluye todos los suministros médicos necesarios para tratar lesiones y dolencias por tu cuenta.</Spanish>
		</Key>
		<Key ID="STR_WL_ShopDescriptions_fuelFull">
			<English>25 litres of pure unleaded fuel!</English>
		</Key>
		<Key ID="STR_WL_ShopDescriptions_fuelEmpty">
			<English>Empty fuel can. You can refill it!</English>
		</Key>
		<Key ID="STR_WL_ShopDescriptions_spawnBeacon">
			<English>Choose your spawn location. Disclaimer: This product does not guarantee safe delivery of goods.</English>
		</Key>
		<Key ID="STR_WL_ShopDescriptions_SyphonHose">
			<English>Go forth and steal fuel from vehicles!</English>
		</Key>
		<Key ID="STR_WL_ShopDescriptions_Energy_Drink">
			<English>Allows you to sprint continuously for 5 minutes.</English>
		</Key>
		<Key ID="STR_WL_ShopDescriptions_Warchest">
			<English>A safe to store your team's money.</English>
		</Key>
	</Package>
	<Package name="Dialogs">
		<Key ID="STR_WL_dialog_TeamkillText">
			<English>Your teammate %2 player %1 has killed you (Friendly Fire).&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;If it was an accident, forgive them; however, they owe you an explanation.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;If they do not apologize, punish them.</English>
			<Spanish>Tu compañero %2 jugador %1 te ha matado (Fuego Amigo).&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Si fue un accidente, perdónalo; sin embargo, él te debe una explicación.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Si no se disculpa, castígalo.</Spanish>
		</Key>
	</Package>
	<Package name="Errors">
		<Key ID="STR_WL_Errors_InProgress">
			<English>You are already performing another action!</English>
		</Key>
		<Key ID="STR_WL_Errors_InVehicle">
			<English>You are currently busy!</English>
		</Key>
		<Key ID="STR_WL_Errors_BeaconActive">
			<English>You already have an active spawn beacon!</English>
		</Key>
		<Key ID="STR_WL_Errors_BeaconInVehicle">
			<English>You cannot enter a vehicle while placing a spawn beacon!</English>
		</Key>
		<Key ID="STR_WL_Errors_BeaconTooMany">
			<English>You cannot take more spawn beacons!</English>
		</Key>
	</Package>
</Project>
